<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Generated by adevtool; do not edit
     For more info, see https://github.com/kdrag0n/adevtool -->
<resources>
  <dimen name="face_enroll_intro_illustration_margin_bottom">-15dp</dimen>
  <dimen name="face_preview_scale">1</dimen>
  <dimen name="face_preview_translate_x">-130</dimen>
  <dimen name="face_preview_translate_y">-300</dimen>
  <dimen name="udfps_lottie_translate_y">16776716.000000dp</dimen>
  <string name="biometrics_unlock_set_unlock_password">Password • Fingerprint • Face</string>
  <string name="biometrics_unlock_set_unlock_pattern">Pattern • Fingerprint • Face</string>
  <string name="biometrics_unlock_set_unlock_pin">PIN • Fingerprint • Face</string>
  <string name="config_face_enroll_traffic_light_package">com.google.android.settings.future.biometrics.faceenroll</string>
  <string name="suggested_fingerprint_lock_settings_title">Use Fingerprint Unlock</string>
  <integer-array name="face_enroll_primary_buckets">
    <item>2</item>
    <item>7</item>
    <item>12</item>
    <item>17</item>
  </integer-array>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_consent_introduction_title">Allow Face Unlock</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_education_message">On the next screen, rotate your head to capture all angles of your face</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_education_message_accessibility">On the next screen, hold your phone at eye level</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_finish_title">Looks good!</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_accessibility">Setup for limited vision or head motion</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_accessibility_expanded">When using Face Unlock, your head may need to be more directly in front of your phone.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_accessibility_vision">Require eyes open</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_consent_message">Using your child’s face to unlock their phone may be less secure than a strong pattern or PIN.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_control_consent_message">You and your child can delete their face model or turn off Face Unlock at any time in Settings. Face models are stored on the phone until they’re deleted.\n\nLearn more at g.co/pixel/faceunlock.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_control_consent_title">You and your child are in control</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_control_message">You can delete your face model or turn off Face Unlock at any time in Settings. Face models are stored on the phone until you delete them.\n\nLearn more at g.co/pixel/faceunlock.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_control_title">You’re in control</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_how_consent_message">Face Unlock creates a unique model of your child’s face to verify it’s them. To create this face model during setup, your child will take images of their face from different angles.\n\nWhen they use Face Unlock, images are used to update their face model. Images used to create their face model are not stored, but the face model is stored securely on the phone and never leaves the phone. All processing occurs securely on the phone.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_how_message">Face Unlock creates a unique model of your face to verify it’s you. To create this face model during setup, you will take images of your face from different angles.\n\nWhen you use Face Unlock, images are used to update your face model. Images used to create your face model are not stored, but the face model is stored securely on your phone and never leaves the phone. All processing occurs securely on your phone.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_how_title">How it works</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_consent_gaze">Face Unlock can require your child’s eyes to be open to unlock the phone or verify it’s them. You and your child can turn this option on at any time in Settings.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_consent_glasses">If your child normally wears eyeglasses, they can wear them during setup.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_consent_less_secure">Using your child’s face to unlock their phone may be less secure than a strong pattern, PIN, or password</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_consent_looking">Looking at the phone can unlock it even when they don’t intend to. Their phone can also be unlocked by someone who looks a lot like them, like an identical sibling, or if someone holds it up to their face.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_gaze">Face Unlock can require your eyes to be open to unlock the phone or verify it’s you. You can turn this option on at any time in Settings.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_less_secure">Using your face to unlock your phone may be less secure than a strong pattern, PIN, or password</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_looking">Looking at the phone can unlock it even when you don’t intend to. Your phone can also be unlocked by someone who looks a lot like you, like an identical sibling, or if someone holds it up to your face.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_title">Keep in mind</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_education_title_accessibility">How to set up Face Unlock</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_finish_description">Now you can pick up your phone and use your face to unlock it</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_improve_face_alert_body">Delete your current face model to set up Face Unlock again.\n\nYour face model will be permanently and securely deleted.\n\nAfter deletion, you will need your PIN, pattern, or password to unlock your phone.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_improve_face_alert_body_fingerprint">Delete your current face model to set up Face Unlock again.\n\nYour face model will be permanently and securely deleted.\n\nAfter deletion, you will need your fingerprint, PIN, pattern, or password to unlock your phone.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_glasses">If you normally wear eyeglasses, you can wear them during setup.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_message">Use your face to unlock your phone</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_settings_footer">Use your face to unlock your phone.\n\nKeep in mind:\nYou can only have one face set up at a time. To add another face, delete the current one.\n\nLooking at the phone can unlock it when you don’t intend to.\n\nYour phone can be unlocked by someone else if it’s held up to your face.\n\nYour phone can be unlocked by someone who looks a lot like you, like an identical sibling.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_settings_footer_attention_not_supported">Use your face to unlock your phone.\n\nKeep in mind:\nYou can only have one face set up at a time. To add another face, delete the current one.\n\nLooking at the phone can unlock it when you don’t intend to.\n\nYour phone can be unlocked by someone else if it’s held up to your face, even if your eyes are closed.\n\nYour phone can be unlocked by someone who looks a lot like you, like an identical sibling.</string>
  <string name="security_settings_face_settings_require_attention_details">To unlock the phone, your eyes must be open. For best results, take off sunglasses when unlocking the phone.</string>
</resources>
